export const data=[
    {
        question : "For the expression (7-(4*5))+(9/3) which of the following is the post order tree traversal?",
        option1: "*745-93/+",
        option2: "93/+745*-",
        option3: "745*-93/+",
        option4: "74*+593/-",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question : "The time complexity of calculating the sum of all leaf nodes in an n-order binary tree is __________",
        option1: "O(n^2)",
        option2: "O(n+1)",
        option3: "O(1)",
        option4: "O(n)",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question : "What is a full binary tree?",
        option1: "Each node has exactly zero or two children",
        option2: "Each node has exactly two children",
        option3: "All the leaves are at the same level",
        option4: "Each node has exactly one or two children",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question : "Which of the following is not an advantage of trees?",
        option1: "Hierarchial structure",
        option2: "Faster search",
        option3: "Router algorithms",
        option4: "Undo/Redo operations in notepad",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question : "In a full binary tree if there are L leaves, then total number of nodes N are?",
        option1: "N = 2*L",
        option2: "N = L + 1",
        option3: "N = L - 1",
        option4: "N = 2*L - 1",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question : "Level of a node is distance from root to that node. For example, level of root is 1 and levels of left and right children of root is 2. The maximum number of nodes on level i of a binary tree is (In the following answers, the operator \'^\' indicates power).",
        option1: "2^(i-1)",
        option2: "2^i",
        option3: "2^(i+1)",
        option4: "2^[(i+1)/2]",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question : "If arity of operators is fixed, then which of the following notations can be used to parse expressions without parentheses? a) Infix Notation (Inorder traversal of a expression tree) b) Postfix Notation (Postorder traversal of a expression tree) c) Prefix Notation (Preorder traversal of a expression tree)",
        option1: "b and c",
        option2: "Only b",
        option3: "a, b and c",
        option4: "None of them",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question : "In a complete k-ary tree, every internal node has exactly k children or no child. The number of leaves in such a tree with n internal nodes is:",
        option1: "nk",
        option2: "(n-1)k+1",
        option3: "n(k-1)+1",
        option4: "n(k-1)",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question : "The maximum number of binary trees that can be formed with three unlabelled nodes is:",
        option1: "1",
        option2: "5",
        option3: "4",
        option4: "3",
        ans: 5,
    },
    {
        question : "Breadth First Search (BFS) is started on a binary tree beginning from the root vertex. There is a vertex t at a distance four from the root. If t is the n-th vertex in this BFS traversal, then the maximum possible value of n is ________",
        option1: "15",
        option2: "16",
        option3: "31",
        option4: "32",
        ans: 31,
    },
];